var questions = [
	{	//1
		"question": "How many stop signs are there in the city of Paris?",
		"option1": "1,000",
		"option2": "100",
		"option3": "10",
		"option4": "1",
		"answer": "4"
	},
	{	//2
		"question": "When the Spanish settled in San Francisco, what was its original name?",
		"option1": "Yerba Buena",
		"option2": "Mocha Latte",
		"option3": "Bueno Sera",
		"option4": "Burro Yerba",
		"answer": "1"
	},
	{	//3
		"question": "What do many Poles enjoy doing in the summertime?",
		"option1": "rollerskating",
		"option2": "mushroom picking",
		"option3": "drinking wine",
		"option4": "bull fighting",
		"answer": "2"
	},
	{	//4
		"question": " ______ was used as binding material to stick bricks together for the Great Wall",
		"option1": "Scotch tape",
		"option2": "mortar",
		"option3": "hot glue",
		"option4": "sticky rice flour ",
		"answer": "4"
	},
	{	//5
		"question": "Canadians consume the most __________ in the world",
		"option1": "mac and cheese",
		"option2": "maple syrup",
		"option3": "bacon",
		"option4": "peanut butter",
		"answer": "1"
	},
	{	//6
		"question": "Italians typically don't drink coffee after _________",
		"option1": "10 AM",
		"option2": "11 AM",
		"option3": "12 PM",
		"option4": "1 PM",
		"answer": "2"
	},
	{	//7
		"question": "What days are Moroccan weekends?",
		"option1": "Monday and Tuesday",
		"option2": "Wednesday and Thursday",
		"option3": "Thursday and Friday",
		"option4": "Saturday and Sunday",
		"answer": "3"
	},
	{	//8
		"question": "There are over _______ different varieties of Potato grown in Peru",
		"option1": "3",
		"option2": "30",
		"option3": "300",
		"option4": "3,000",
		"answer": "4"
	},
	{	//9
		"question": "Niue's currency does not feature... ",
		"option1": "Disney characters",
		"option2": "Pokemon characters",
		"option3": "Teen Titan characters",
		"option4": "Star Wars characters",
		"answer": "3"
	},
	{	//10
		"question": "There is a house in Rockport that was built in 1922 entirely out of __________",
		"option1": "sticks",
		"option2": "straw",
		"option3": "bricks",
		"option4": "newspapers",
		"answer": "4"
	},
	{	//11
		"question": "Bhutan is the only country to measure Gross National __________ ",
		"option1": "Productivity",
		"option2": "Happiness",
		"option3": "Sadness",
		"option4": "Efficiency",
		"answer": "2"
	},
	{	//12
		"question": "It is said that you can hear your own __________ in the Kalahari Desert",
		"option1": "thoughts",
		"option2": "heart beat",
		"option3": "pulse",
		"option4": "blood flow",
		"answer": "4"
	},
	{	//13
		"question": " ___________ of Libya is desert land, covered all with sand",
		"option1": "10%",
		"option2": "50%",
		"option3": "75%",
		"option4": "99%",
		"answer": "4"
	},
	{	//14
		"question": "Selling, importing or spitting out _____________ is illegal in Singapore",
		"option1": "chewing gum",
		"option2": "noodles",
		"option3": "candy",
		"option4": "apples",
		"answer": "1"
	},
	{	//15
		"question": "A shepherd discovered __________ in Ethiopia when his goats ate its leaves",
		"option1": "sugar cane",
		"option2": "coffee",
		"option3": "goji berries",
		"option4": "wheat",
		"answer": "2"
	},
	{	//16
		"question": "The clearest lake in the world is in...",
		"option1": "The United States of America ",
		"option2": "New Zealand",
		"option3": "Iceland",
		"option4": "Vietnam",
		"answer": "2"
	},
	{	//17
		"question": "People in _______ help pedestrians and direct road safety in La Paz",
		"option1": "bright yellow vests",
		"option2": "the police force",
		"option3": "the fire department",
		"option4": "zebra costumes",
		"answer": "4"
	},
	{	//18
		"question": "There are more __________ than people in Amsterdam",
		"option1": "houses",
		"option2": "bikes",
		"option3": "bridges",
		"option4": "elephants",
		"answer": "2"
	},
	{	//19
		"question": "Babies are _____________ for good luck in Solapur, India",
		"option1": "dropped from a 30ft building",
		"option2": "given tea leaves",
		"option3": "elegantly dressed",
		"option4": "fed 10 times a day",
		"answer": "1"
	},
	{	//20
		"question": "An average wedding lasts __________ in Yemen",
		"option1": "7 days",
		"option2": "14 days",
		"option3": "21 days",
		"option4": "28 days",
		"answer": "3"
	},

	
]